https://www.rmsdrill.com/privacy-policy/

Email
(800) 605-1608
Get QuoteSkip to content
ServicesMarching Band DrillHorn Line VisualsCustom Color Guard ChoreographySmall and Young Band InformationVisuals DVD and Pose BookDrill ExamplesAnimated Pyware Drill ExamplesContest Performance ExamplesTestimonialsAbout UsWho We Are
Click to Get QuotePrivacy PolicyRMS Visual Designs is committed to protecting your privacy. We collect and use information volunteered privately by you to provide personalized estimates and services to you while assisting us in establishing our online presence. We have created and adopted this Website Privacy Policy (“Policy”) to cement our current data collection, disclosure policies and practices for this website and its related web pages (the “Site”).ConsentBy using this Site, you consent to this Policy. Please refrain from the use of the Site if you are not in agreement to this Policy. Information gathered from the Site will be stored and processed primarily in the United States of America. If you access the Site from outside the United States of America, your use of the Site constitutes consent to transfer information to the United States of America. This Site is not intended for children.Google Analytics (Google)Google Analytics is a web analysis service provided by Google Inc. (“Google”). Google utilizes the data collected to track and examine the use of this website, to prepare reports on its activities and share them with other Google services. Google may use the data collected to contextualize and personalize ads of its own advertising network. Personal data collected: cookie and usage data. United States of America – Privacy Policy – Opt. OutGoogle Maps API (Google)Google Maps API is a maps visualization service provided by Google Inc. (“Google”). We use this service to incorporate maps providing you with directions on how to arrive at our locations. Google may use the data collected to contextualize and personalize ads of its own advertising network. Personal data collected: cookie and usage data. United States of America – Privacy Policy – Opt. OutCollection of InformationWe may collect personally identifiable information from users at certain locations on the Site (such as your name, address, e-mail and telephone number). This information is voluntarily added by the user, therefore, it is your choice whether to provide us with this information or not. We may also collect non-personal and anonymous information from users. This information is used to compile aggregate data that will not be sold, transferred or released to any third party unless you have requested we do so. For example, we may collect system-related information, such as IP address, browser type and operating system type, to be used for system administration purposes, to help diagnose problems with our servers, to monitor traffic patterns, to determine which services are used most frequently and to assess Site usage. We may retain information we gather about you indefinitely.CookiesWe may occasionally also elect to use “cookies” for the convenience of our users. We use cookies to create a custom experience for the user if they have already entered personal information to the Site. A cookie is a small text file that is recorded either temporarily or persistently on your hard drive by a web page server. Cookies are not used to deliver viruses or other harmful programs that would cause damage to your computer or load time. Rather, cookies enable us to recognize a user without requiring the user to repeatedly log in when using the Site. Additionally, cookies may allow us to monitor traffic patterns, Site usage, and session information to make the Site more useful for the end user in the long term.Most browsers accept cookies automatically. Any user can alter the browser’s setting to decline cookies. You may be able to modify your browser settings to notify you each time a cookie is created. This would allow the user to accept or decline cookies on an individual basis.Use of InformationIn addition to the uses described above, we may use the information we receive from you to:Process estimate requests: To fulfill these requests the following information is generally needed: name, phone number, e-mail address and any other pertinent information. This also allows us and our company to contact you with requested information.Process your request for free brochures or newsletters. We need to know your name, e-mail, address, phone number, mailing address and any other related information.Monitor traffic patterns and Site use of customers in order to develop the design and layout of our online presence; andUse the collected addresses or email addresses of our customers to send them printed or online communications.Disclosure of InformationWe may disclose personally identifiable and aggregate anonymous information to companies, agents, contractors, or others hired to perform functions on our behalf or represent RMS Visual Designs. These companies, agents, contractors, or others may be permitted access to personal information to perform functions for you or this business. We may also disclose personally identifiable information to regulatory and credit agencies if it is deemed appropriate.If one of our business lines or the entire business, or a substantial portion thereof, is acquired or transferred, whether by merger, consolidation or purchase of a substantial portion of assets, we may disclose and transfer your personally identifiable information to the acquiring third party.We may also disclose aggregate anonymous information to our clients, business partners, merchants, advertisers, investors, potential buyers and other third parties if we deem such disclosure, in our discretion, to have sound business reasons or justification.When you access the Site through any co-branded websites or linked web pages, your personal information may be disclosed to and become the property of us and/or the relevant co-sponsor. In that case, the use of your personally identifiable information by the co-sponsor company will be subject to the privacy policy of that company. We are not responsible for, nor subject to the co-sponsors policy use, of your personal information. Before entering our website through a co-sponsor, we encourage you to review the privacy policies and practices of any relevant co-sponsor before supplying any personal information.Policy ChangesWe reserve the right to change this Policy at any time and at our discretion. We may modify this Policy to reflect changes in the way we collect, use or disclose information. We may also modify this Policy based around any changes in privacy laws, regulation and/or industry standards, we recommend and encourage you to review this Policy when accessing the Site or disclosing personal or aggregate information. Continued access to and use of the Site after Site changes have been made is considered an automatic acceptance of any changes that have been made.Applicable LawThis Policy shall be governed by the laws of the State of Texas, without regard to conflicts of law principles, and exclusive jurisdiction and venue for any dispute arising out of this Policy shall be the state courts or district federal courts of Texas.Tight Budget?Save15%Book by May 30th and receive 15% off!
Get QuoteWhy Choose RMSSuccess is always my top priority for you and your students. Award Winning Proven DesignsOn-Time Delivery / Fast Turnaround30 Years of ExperienceNo Ghost Writers!Guard and Percussion Fully IntegratedRe-size service if Section Totals ChangeDesigned with Pyware 3DAFFORDABLE Prices Starting at $500Unlimited Consultation and Support throughout Marching SeasonIs it better to hire a local designer?In most cases, NO!
It’s been my experience that local or novice designers add no value to the equation when putting together a marching band show. Many of these designers also work for several bands that you will see all season. They offer the benefit of coming to rehearsal as a bonus. Actually being on-site or attending rehearsals is NOT needed with my designs!I’ve worked successfully with many clients located in every corner of the US with no problems or delays. I can bring a fresh approach to your drill and visual program.My distance from your location is simply a
non-issue.Client Testimonials
“Robert is a true professional. The marching band drill we received from him was on-time, complete and without error. He incorporated every concept we requested and followed all of the guidelines that we set...”
- Jason Boyden Mona Shores High School, Michigan (118+ Marching)
Read Testimonials
RMS Drill
4.8All of my drills are designed exclusively using the latest version of Pyware.
RMS Visual Designs provides Custom Marching Band Drill for bands at all sizes & difficulty levels. Over 2,700 superior ratings and high contest placements.
Contact Us(800) 605-1608
AddressDallas, TX 75219
HoursMonday - Friday
6 AM - 9 PM CST
EmailRobert@RMSdrill.comAdditional LinksHomePrivacy PolicyTerms of ServiceSitemap
© 2020 RMS Visual Design
Site Designed and Optimized by Ottaway Digital
© 2020 RMS Visual Design
Site Designed and Optimized by Ottaway Digital
Get A QuoteFill out the form below to receive a fast, customized price quote.Exact section totals and show music DO NOT have to be finalized.
I only need approximate section totals to give you an exact price.Get Quote
(Must be accurate)
Mobile Number
(If provided, I will send a text to let you know the quote has been sent.)
WINDS marching
*
(Approximate Number)
PERCUSSION marching
*
(Approximate Number)
GUARD marching
*
(Approximate Number)
Include the price for Horn Line Visuals in the quote?
*
Yes
No
Include the price for Custom Guard Choreography?
*
Yes
No
Other Info, special considerations: show music, expectations for the drill, etc: (optional)
Discount code or tell me how you found my website for 15% off
Book by May 30th and receive 15% off!Submit
If you are human, leave this field blank.
×
